<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Learn vRealize Automation</title><link>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Learn vRealize Automation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Learn Cloud Assembly</title><link>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learncloudassembly/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learncloudassembly/</guid><description>Welcome to Learn Cloud Assembly! This site is designed as a living technical reference focussed on providing in-depth information for the Cloud Assembly User - whether you’re new to Cloud Assembly or an expert at using cloud templates and extensibility.</description></item><item><title>Learn Code Stream</title><link>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learncodestream/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learncodestream/</guid><description>Welcome to Learn Code Stream! This site is designed as a living technical reference focussed on providing in-depth information for the Code Stream developer - whether you’re new to Code Stream or an experienced developer.</description></item><item><title>Learn SaltStack Config</title><link>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learnsaltstackconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learnsaltstackconfig/</guid><description>Welcome to Learn SaltStack Config! This site is designed as a living technical reference focussed on providing in-depth information for the SaltStack Config Administrtor - whether you’re new to SaltStack Config or experienced SaltStack configuration management.</description></item><item><title>Learn Service Broker</title><link>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learnservicebroker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learnservicebroker/</guid><description>Welcome to Learn Service Broker! This site is designed as a living technical reference focussed on providing in-depth information for the Service Broker Catalog and Policy service in vRealize Automation - whether you’re new to Service Broker or an experert at provide service catalogs to your users.</description></item><item><title>Learn vRealize Orchestrator</title><link>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learnorchestrator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnvrealizeautomation.github.io/posts/learnorchestrator/</guid><description>Welcome to Learn vRealize Orchestrator! This site is designed as a living technical reference focussed on providing in-depth information for the Orchestrator (vRO) developer - whether you’re new to Orchestrator or an experienced vRO workflow developer.</description></item></channel></rss>